<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.megatome.frame2.wsfeature"
      label="Frame2 Web Services"
      version="1.2.3"
      provider-name="Megatome Technologies"
      plugin="org.megatome.frame2ws"
      os="linux,macosx,solaris,win32"
      ws="carbon,gtk,motif,win32"
      nl="en"
      arch="ia64,ppc,sparc,x86"
      image="frame2logo_med.jpg">

   <description>
      Adds support to the Frame2 plugin for Web Services.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2004-2007 Megatome Technologies
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Frame2 Open Source License
Copyright (c) 2004-2007 Megatome Technologies.  All rights reserved.
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
3. The end-user documentation included with the redistribution,
if any, must include the following acknowlegement: &quot;This product
includes software developed by Megatome Technologies.&quot; Alternately,
this acknowlegement may appear in the software itself, if and
wherever such third-party acknowlegements normally appear.
4. The names &quot;The Frame2 Project&quot;, and &quot;Frame2&quot;, must not be
used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
without prior written permission. For written permission, please
contact iamthechad@sourceforge.net.
5. Products derived from this software may not be called &quot;Frame2&quot;
nor may &quot;Frame2&quot; appear in their names without prior written
permission of Megatome Technologies.
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.
IN NO EVENT SHALL MEGATOME TECHNOLOGIES OR ITS CONTRIBUTORS BE
LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY,
OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT
OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS;
OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF
THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
This product includes software developed by Virtuas Solutions,
LLC.
Frame2 is based upon the TurboM2 framework. For more information
about TurboM2, visit http://www.turbom2.org
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Frame2 Update Site" url="http://frame2.megatome.com/eclipse"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.megatome.frame2"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.launching"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import feature="org.megatome.frame2.feature" version="1.4.3"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.megatome.frame2ws"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
